final List<Map<String, dynamic>> cppQuiz = [
  {
    'question': 'What is C++?',
    'options': ['Programming Language', 'Framework', 'Database', 'Library'],
    'correctAnswer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Who is the creator of C++?',
    'options': [
      'Dennis Ritchie',
      'Bjarne Stroustrup',
      'James Gosling',
      'Guido van Rossum'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of these is a feature of C++?',
    'options': [
      'Object-Oriented',
      'Functional',
      'Procedural',
      'All of the above'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 3,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which symbol is used for comments in C++?',
    'options': ['#', '//', '/* */', 'Both // and /* */'],
    'correctAnswer': 3,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the file extension for C++ source files?',
    'options': ['.c', '.cpp', '.hpp', '.java'],
    'correctAnswer': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of these is a valid C++ data type?',
    'options': ['int', 'char', 'bool', 'All of the above'],
    'correctAnswer': 3,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which keyword is used to define a class in C++?',
    'options': ['class', 'struct', 'object', 'define'],
    'correctAnswer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the starting point of a C++ program?',
    'options': ['start()', 'main()', 'init()', 'None of the above'],
    'correctAnswer': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of these is used to allocate memory dynamically in C++?',
    'options': ['alloc()', 'malloc()', 'new', 'create'],
    'correctAnswer': 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which operator is used to access members of a class?',
    'options': ['.', '->', '::', 'All of the above'],
    'correctAnswer': 3,
  },
];
